(self.webpackChunk_N_E=self.webpackChunk_N_E||[]).push([[387],{3077:function(e,n,s){"use strict";s.r(n),s.d(n,{default:function(){return u}});var r=s(7812),t=s(1664),a=s(1163),o=s(9008),i=s(7294),l=JSON.parse('[0,{"1":[{"question":"What type of framework is Next.js2?","answerOptions":[{"answer":"Frontend"},{"answer":"Backend"},{"answer":"FullStack","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"None of the above"}]},{"question":"When was Next.js released?","answerOptions":[{"answer":"20 September 2019"},{"answer":"14 January 2017"},{"answer":"25 October 2016","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"28 March 2018"}]},{"question":"When was Next.js released?","answerOptions":[{"answer":"20 September 2019"},{"answer":"14 January 2017"},{"answer":"25 October 2016","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"28 March 2018"}]},{"question":"Which CSS Framework are we using?","answerOptions":[{"answer":"Bootstrap"},{"answer":"TailwindCSS","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"Chakra UI"},{"answer":"Bulma CSS"}]},{"question":"Which class in Tailwind is used to set flex direction of column?","answerOptions":[{"answer":"col"},{"answer":"col-flex"},{"answer":"flex-col","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"None of the above"}]},{"question":"What type of framework is Next.js?","answerOptions":[{"answer":"Frontend"},{"answer":"Backend"},{"answer":"FullStack","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"None of the above"}]},{"question":"When was Next.js released?","answerOptions":[{"answer":"20 September 2019"},{"answer":"14 January 2017"},{"answer":"25 October 2016","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"28 March 2018"}]},{"question":"Which CSS Framework are we using?","answerOptions":[{"answer":"Bootstrap"},{"answer":"TailwindCSS","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"Chakra UI"},{"answer":"Bulma CSS"}]},{"question":"Which class in Tailwind is used to set flex direction of column?","answerOptions":[{"answer":"col"},{"answer":"col-flex"},{"answer":"flex-col","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"None of the above"}]},{"question":"What type of framework is Next.js?","answerOptions":[{"answer":"Frontend"},{"answer":"Backend"},{"answer":"FullStack","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"None of the above"}]}]}]'),c=s(5893),u=function(e){var n=(0,a.useRouter)().query.quiz;Array.isArray(n)&&(n=n.join("")),console.log(n);var s=parseInt(n)-1;console.log(s);var u=l[1][1],w=(0,i.useState)(0),d=w[0],h=w[1],x=(0,i.useState)([]),f=x[0],m=x[1],p=(0,i.useState)(0),b=p[0],j=p[1],N=(0,i.useState)(!1),v=N[0],g=N[1],C=function(){var e=d-1;e>=0&&h(e)},k=function(e){m([f[d]={answerByUser:e}]),m((0,r.Z)(f)),console.log(f)};return(0,c.jsxs)("div",{children:[(0,c.jsxs)(o.default,{children:[(0,c.jsxs)("title",{children:[" Level ",n," "]}),(0,c.jsx)("meta",{name:"description",content:"Quest Topix"})]}),(0,c.jsx)("div",{className:"flex justify-center h-full w-full",children:(0,c.jsx)("div",{className:"flex w-3/4 h-full justify-evenly bg-black bg-opacity-50 backdrop-blur-xl rounded-lg drop-shadow-lg text-white m-5 rounded",children:(0,c.jsxs)("div",{className:"flex flex-col justify-center items-center p-3",children:[(0,c.jsx)("div",{className:"text-xl font-bold mb-3",children:"Quest"}),v?(0,c.jsxs)(c.Fragment,{children:[(0,c.jsxs)("h1",{className:"text-3xl font-semibold text-center text-white",children:["You scored ",b," out of ",u.length]}),b<8?(0,c.jsx)("h1",{className:"text-3xl font-semibold text-center text-white",children:"You didn't pass this round."}):(0,c.jsx)("button",{onClick:C,className:"w-[49%] py-3 bg-indigo-600 rounded-lg",children:"Upload"}),(0,c.jsx)(t.default,{href:"/quest",children:(0,c.jsx)("a",{className:"w-[49%] py-3 bg-indigo-600 rounded-lg",children:"Retry"})})]}):(0,c.jsx)(c.Fragment,{children:(0,c.jsxs)("div",{className:"flex flex-col items-start w-full",children:[(0,c.jsxs)("h4",{className:"mt-10 text-xl text-white/60",children:["Question ",d+1," of ",u.length]}),(0,c.jsx)("div",{className:"mt-4 text-2xl text-white",children:u[d].question}),(0,c.jsx)("div",{className:"flex flex-col w-full",children:u[d].answerOptions.map((function(e,n){var s;return(0,c.jsxs)("div",{className:"flex items-center w-full py-4 pl-5 m-2 ml-0 space-x-2 border-2 cursor-pointer border-white/10 rounded-xl bg-white/5",onClick:function(n){return k(e.answer)},children:[(0,c.jsx)("input",{type:"radio",name:e.answer,value:e.answer,onChange:function(n){return k(e.answer)},checked:e.answer===(null===(s=f[d])||void 0===s?void 0:s.answerByUser),className:"w-6 h-6 bg-black"}),(0,c.jsx)("p",{className:"ml-6 text-white",children:e.answer})]},n)}))}),(0,c.jsxs)("div",{className:"flex justify-between w-full mt-4 text-white",children:[(0,c.jsx)("button",{onClick:C,className:"w-[49%] py-3 bg-indigo-600 rounded-lg",children:"Previous"}),(0,c.jsx)("button",{onClick:d+1===u.length?function(){for(var e=0,n=function(n){u[n].answerOptions.map((function(s){var r;return s.isCorrect&&s.answer===(null===(r=f[n])||void 0===r?void 0:r.answerByUser)&&(e+=1)}))},s=0;s<u.length;s++)n(s);j(e),g(!0)}:function(){var e=d+1;e<u.length&&h(e)},className:"w-[49%] py-3 bg-indigo-600 rounded-lg",children:d+1===u.length?"Submit":"Next"})]})]})})]})})})]})}},9434:function(e,n,s){(window.__NEXT_P=window.__NEXT_P||[]).push(["/[quiz]",function(){return s(3077)}])},1163:function(e,n,s){e.exports=s(9898)}},function(e){e.O(0,[774,888,179],(function(){return n=9434,e(e.s=n);var n}));var n=e.O();_N_E=n}]);